[
  {
    "question": " Is it possible to have an activity without UI to perform action/actions?",

    "option1": " Not possible",

    "option2": " Wrong question",

    "option3": " Yes, it is possible",

    "option4": " None of the above",

    "answer": " Yes, it is possible"
  },
  {
    "question": " On which thread services work in android?",

    "option1": " Worker Thread",

    "option2": " Own Thread",

    "option3": " Main Thread",

    "option4": " None of the above",

    "answer": " Main Thread"
  },
  {
    "question": " What are the return values of onStartCommand() in android services?",

    "option1": " START_STICKY",

    "option2": " START_NOT_STICKY",

    "option3": " START_REDELIVER_INTENT",

    "option4": " All of the above",

    "answer": " All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question": " What is the time limit of broadcast receiver in android?",

    "option1": " 10 sec",

    "option2": " 15 sec",

    "option3": " 5 sec",

    "option4": " 1 hour",

    "answer": " 10 sec"
  },
  {
    "question": " What is the application class in android?",

    "option1": " class that can create only an object",

    "option2": " Anonymous class",

    "option3": " Java class",

    "option4": " Base class for all classes",

    "answer": " Base class for all classes"
  },
  {
    "question": " Which method is used to find GPS enabled or disabled pro-grammatically in android?",

    "option1": " finish()",

    "option2": " getGPSStatus()",

    "option3": " onProviderDisable()",

    "option4": " getGPS()",

    "answer": " onProviderDisable()"
  },
  {
    "question": " Data can be read from local source XML in android through",

    "option1": " XML resource parser",

    "option2": " XML pull parsing",

    "option3": " DOM parsing",

    "option4": " None of the above",

    "answer": " XML resource parser"
  },

  {
    "question": " How to find the JSON element length in android JSON?",

    "option1": " count()",

    "option2": " sum()",

    "option3": " add()",

    "option4": " length()",

    "answer": " length()"
  },
  {
    "question": " What is transient data in android?",

    "option1": " Permanent data",

    "option2": " Secure data",

    "option3": " Temporary data",

    "option4": " Logical data",

    "answer": " Logical data"
  },
  {
    "question": " What is a thread in android?",

    "option1": " Same as services",

    "option2": " Background activity",

    "option3": " Broadcast Receiver",

    "option4": " Independent dis-patchable unit is called a thread",

    "answer": " Independent dis-patchable unit is called a thread"
  }
]
